export const verbPracticeDataBrezhoneg = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Me", answer: "zo" },
    { prompt: "Te", answer: "oc'h" },
    { prompt: "E単", answer: "eo" },
    { prompt: "Hi", answer: "eo" },
    { prompt: "O", answer: "eo" },
    { prompt: "zo", answer: "me" },
    { prompt: "oc'h", answer: "te" },
    { prompt: "eo", answer: "e単/hi/o" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Me", answer: "o" },
    { prompt: "Te", answer: "oc'h" },
    { prompt: "E単", answer: "he" },
    { prompt: "Hi", answer: "he" },
    { prompt: "o", answer: "me/te/e単/hi/o" }
  ]
};
